So, you want to know how to keep your teeth white naturally.
Well, my name's Michelle, and I'm a Dental Assistant with Solutionz, and I'm going to explain that for you.
There's several different methods and ways on how to keep your teeth white naturally.
One is that you can eat a lot of raw vegetables.
That will keep all the bacteria and debris from sticking to your teeth, which then in return produces like a yellow film on your teeth, or you can actually mix salt and lemon together and create like a paste, and brush your teeth with that.
That's a natural form on how to keep your teeth white.
It doesn't taste as great, but you would then want to of course wash your mouth out immediately with water, and then brush your teeth with your regular toothpaste.
There is over-the-counter toothpaste that you can get for that to help your keep, keep your teeth white.
You also might want to rinse with hydrogen peroxide.
That is a great form on how to keep your teeth white naturally.
You can brush your teeth with it; create like a bubble effect on your teeth.
Actually, you can let it sit there for about a few minutes, and then rinse your mouth out with water.
You can gargle with hydrogen peroxide.
That will help with keeping your teeth white naturally.
But other than that, those are the main things on how to keep your teeth white naturally.
And once again, my name's Michelle, and I'm with Solutionz, and I just explained to you on how to keep your teeth white naturally.